[music]
>> He is a man who leads a life of danger.
Everyone he [music] meets he says is a
stranger.
On every movie he makes
>> [music]
>> another chance he takes.
He knows all he wanted to see and
follow.
Secret
agent man, secret
>> [music]
>> agent man.
They tell
you a number. [singing]
I know they've taken away.
Somebody's eating my underwear.
Here piggy piggy piggy chap oh.
Mom, before she starts there isn't a
shred of evidence to support her
allegations.
>> Gillian, your son is a psycho. He booby
trapped my hair dryer. Nice hypothesis,
but you can't prove it. Yeah, but I can
hurt you. Mom, Mom,
she needs to be medicated.
Wonderful. Come here.
>> [screaming]
>> I hate this family.
Come here.
That's what you're getting in a time
out.
>> [laughter]
>> Come on guys.
Backpack.
Uh-uh.
What? It's in style. It's inappropriate.
Go put on some jeans.
And spit out the gum.
So, what color do you want to wear
today?
Red, blue, purple? Pink mama, pink.
Faron.
What? You said jeans.
I meant in your size.
Come on guys. Come on, we don't want to
be late.
Go.
Come on sweetie.
No.
Get out.
No fighting.
Allow me.
Hi. Hi. Are we still for dinner?
I'll be there.
We have an audience.
Yuck, I'm going to vomit. He is such a
loser. I like Bob. He's nice. He's a
boring pen importer. He does the same
routine every day. He's like a robot.
That's cuz he is a robot, a cyborg sent
from the future to destroy humanity.
Starting with us.
Well, it's been 3 months. Happy
anniversary.
What is it?
I have to tell you about my job.
This might shock you.
But you should know everything before
this relationship goes further.
Don't, Bob.
What?
I'm very happy when I'm with you. No
one's ever made me laugh like you do.
And if I were a single woman, I could
see a real future for us. But
I'm a package deal.
What do you mean?
My kids are my priority, and
how can I put this gently?
They hate me.
Yeah.
I can make them like me. Oh, see? You
can't make kids like you. Not mine or
anyone's.
My kids have been through a lot, and
I don't think we should take the next
step until they warm up to you.
Doesn't your happiness count?
Excuse me.
Sorry, I've got to go.
Emergency at work.
No ink? Uh
It's much bigger.
Sorry, really.
I will explain everything tomorrow.
Okay.
I'll see you tomorrow.
What took you so long to get here? 60
minutes. Is that for a latte? Oh, I got
it. You're a What What's the expression?
Chopping my boss. Close enough. Pulldark
and a couple other ruskies just went in
the refinery.
Then, I was right.
He's planning something.
Maybe they just want to fill up their
gas tanks for free. I couldn't blame
them.
Nah, that man's so crooked he could eat
nails and poop corkscrews.
You're the world's foremost authority on
Pulldark. What do you think he's up to?
If his mission is to sabotage the
world's oil reserves, why would he care
about some two-bit refinery like this
one?
I'm pretty sure you got a chance to ask
him.
How the heck you going to get in there?
Jetpack?
It's in the shop.
Wait for my signal.
Yuri.
What's this? C4.
When we are done here, I want you to
blow this place to smithereens.
Oh.
>> Yes.
Hurry up.
I don't have all day. There is no
overtime here.
I'm home.
>> [screaming and groaning]
>> I would love to chat, but I got to go.
>> That was fun.
A good aerobic workout.
We should do this again sometime.
Okay, Pol Ard, let's go.
You see the look on Pol Ard's face, man?
>> [cheering]
>> Brilliant work, Bob. Unbelievable. I
really hate [music] to see you go home.
You're the best agent I've ever had.
Hey, you know I'm standing right here.
Maybe I can get your government to loan
you to me just a little bit longer. No.
This was my last assignment. I'm
retiring.
Don't tell me because of Jillian. I want
a normal life.
I want to get married.
Oh, heck, man. Don't get married. Just
find some woman that you're going to
hate in 5 years and give her your house.
Keep the watch.
A memento. Compliments of the CIA.
So, Jillian, is that the woman that
lives next door to your cover house?
Yeah, they've been uh
stiffing out. I could never give up this
life for a woman. We're spies, man.
Every little boy wants to be a spy. It's
the life. All the hours you spend
sitting alone in a little room like
this, eating cold takeout food in the
back of a surveillance van, getting shot
at all the time, learning how to pee in
a bottle in a moving vehicle.
You're doing the right thing.
Only problem is her kids hate me.
You're the man.
Really going to miss you, Hom. Good luck
with those kids.
I brought down dictators.
How tough can three kids be?
>> [screaming]
>> Hi, kids.
I'm sorry about running out last night.
It's all right. It's your job. No, it
was rude. I promise it would never
happen again.
Mom, what about Wingo?
We've tried everything, sweetheart.
He'll come down when he's ready.
Want to see what I've been working on?
Sure.
Wingo, Wingo.
Come on, kitty. It's not that cold.
Please, please, please, Wingo.
There you go.
So, what do you think?
Well,
um
wow. It's a work in progress. Sadly, I
didn't have any time to work on it
today. Cat was on the roof, satellite's
broken again. I spent 2 hours on hold
trying to get a repairman out here. And
I
can't stop thinking about last night.
So,
are we okay?
I understand.
If a man marries you, he marries all of
you.
Don't forget the pig, the cat, and the
turtle.
So,
do you really like it?
It frightens me.
>> [laughter]
>> Sometimes I think I found the last
honest man left in the world.
I brought you all cookies.
Yes? Is it true you're going to marry
Bob? What? Whoa, calm down. You can't do
this, Jillian. You're like so far above
him. What she means is he's boring. He's
a geek. He's a very nice man who treats
me very well. He's a pen importer.
He's a cyborg.
You all don't know him like I do.
He's very passionate about the world and
about my art. He likes to talk about
history, science, and politics. Mhm. I
see what you mean about him not being
boring.
What you all call boring,
I call dependable. For once, I'd like a
man who goes to work every day at the
same time and who comes home every
single night. A man who doesn't lie or
cheat or leave his family the first time
some
My happiness counts, too.
I hate it when all people have feelings.
We got to deep-six Bob.
What's the story here? They hit Podark's
prison transport caravan at the edge of
town. Tell me he didn't get away. Oh,
he's as gone as rum cake at an AA
meeting. I'm telling you this whole
thing was a setup. They knew he was
coming.
Are you saying there's a mole in the
agency? I'm not saying anything except
he got away.
>> Welcome back.
Good chat.
You can't even imagine what it's like in
there.
The oppressive darkness and the torture
of empty days stretching for years.
Prison is hell.
You were in there for 4 hours.
Enough tearful reunion.
I need a new batch of the formula as
soon as possible.
We run another test in 2 days.
I need a change of clothes.
Something current and fashionable.
And something to eat that does not come
with a toy.
Uh
>> [music]
>> Honey, we're getting ready to carve
pumpkins downstairs. Do you want to join
us? Absolutely, cuz I'm a loser and I
have no life.
Did I mention we're going to toast the
pumpkin seeds?
Come on.
I want you to join the family. And I
want some privacy. Don't get fresh with
me. I'll use whatever tone of voice I
want to use with you.
>> Faryn, I want you downstairs.
>> going to come downstairs right now. Get
out.
>> Faryn, this is my house. You will listen
to me.
>> out. Get out. I SAID GET OUT, JILLIAN.
Get out.
>> Downstairs in 5 minutes.
>> I hate this house. I hate this family.
Get out.
No, she won't hear me. I'm on the roof.
It's like the only place I can get any
privacy in this loony bin.
I can't let Jillian marry this guy.
No, it's not that. I mean, you're right.
He is a total drone, but that's not the
issue.
What's going to happen when my dad comes
back?
He won't just leave me here alone. He'll
be back.
And if she's married, what happens then?
I don't know.
Mom, Aunt Feeding Duffle bacon. Okay,
that's just wrong. Why is it wrong?
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, whoa. Whoa. Hey.
So, how's it going with those kids? I'm
taking Julia and the children on a
picnic. I'm going to force those kids to
like me. Force them?
You know, you might as well try
scratching your ear with your elbow.
Guess what?
Pollock escaped.
No longer my problem. Yeah, I know.
But, uh, we recovered a file. Seems to
be an entry portal to a website. But, we
can't crack it.
I thought maybe you could take a look at
it. Hey, if you can figure it out,
great. If you can't, no harm, no foul.
As a favor to you,
send it to my home computer. Already
did.
Oh, while I'm thinking about it,
they suspect there may be a mole at the
agency.
They suspect me? No. You know, Glaze
thinks you're the sharpest barb on the
wire.
I have no idea what that means.
Hey, listen, man. Have fun on your
picnic. Uh, just shoot me back when you
check out that file. Thanks.
I see encryption.
Let's see what you've got.
Is dinner ready? No, I have bad news.
My father's in the hospital. Oh, that's
terrible.
Uh, he plays senior softball and he slid
into third. Now, he's having his hip
replaced.
That's terrible. I have to leave the
kids and fly to Denver to take care of
dad.
That's great.
What are you talking about? Let me watch
the kids. It will give us a chance to
get to know each other. Mhm. No, Bob.
You, them?
I don't know. My aunt's flying in from
San Antonio. She's very good with the
kids. She was in the military. Judith,
this could be just what we need.
You really think you can handle that
kind of pressure?
The driving, the school work, and then
there's Halloween, getting their
costumes, finishing, decorating the
house. No problem. Halloween is my
favorite. You have nothing to worry
about. They'll be perfectly safe with
me.
It's not them I'm worried about.
You can't be serious. Isn't there any
other option? Foster care? Juvenile
hall?
Love you guys.
Going to miss you.
Yeah, as proven by this total
abandonment. You'll survive. I'll buy
you something from the hospital gift
shop. Bye. Love you. See you later. Bye.
So,
is this exciting or what?
Well,
I'll just pack a few things and we'll go
to your house, okay?
Sloppy. I knew he cut his own hair.
Nothing telling in his DVD collection.
Standard action movies, mainstream
comedies, no sci-fi, and nothing above
PG-13.
Hey, his computer. Let's check it out.
>> Good idea. There's got to be some dirt
on there.
Oh, wow. Fashion Armageddon.
I haven't forgotten Cotton. I will look
at the file,
but this is important.
What is a Halloween?
Woah, Faran, do you realize what this
is?
It's got you all worked up. Let me
guess, a Klingon dictionary? You have me
confused with an entirely different
class of geek. Stockholm GBH, grievous
bodily harm live in Stockholm. This is
one of the rarest bootleg concerts in
the world. Why does Bob have it? Who
cares? I'm going to download it.
This is my ticket to coolsville.
This is what you bring me to wear?
You said you wanted coolant.
I look like the Fresh Prince of Belarus.
Send someone out to get me something
elegant.
What is this problem you found?
I went on to download the formula and
found the site being accessed by third
party. If the United States or China has
the formula, they can develop an
antibody for it.
>> the ISP, but it's heavily encrypted. It
will take me a while to track it down.
Find whoever downloaded my formula.
Retrieve it.
And?
Kill them.
Thank you.
What's up with you? I'm going to kill
you. What?
>> I'm going to kill you.
Don't hurt me. Don't hurt me. He's
hurting me. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey.
Hey, stop.
What's going on here? She threw a stink
bomb in my room.
>> What? That's so not true. Oh, so what?
You're saying I threw a stink bomb in my
own room just to get you in trouble?
Sad. So sad.
Barrett.
I'm very disappointed in you.
You two should be in bed by now. Well,
if we finish our homework in time,
Jillian lets us stay up till midnight.
She also likes us to watch Adult Swim.
It's kind of a tradition.
I didn't really think this one through.
>> [snorts]
>> Laura.
Let's get ready for bed.
I don't want to go to
Only my
mommy can dress me.
Laura.
Here I come.
HEY.
COME BACK.
Now I got you.
Come back.
I GOT YOU.
NO, come back.
Laura.
Come on.
Only my
mommy can
Laura.
Only my
mommy can
Mommy can dress
Can your mommy do that?
Sleep.
>> Get out.
Hello.
You're alive. That's a good sign.
How are the kids? We had a great night.
Easy as pie.
Really?
You're with my kids, right?
Bob,
the other night at dinner, you were
going to say something about your job,
and I cut you off.
You want to tell me now?
Uh
it can wait until you get back.
I really think this was a good idea.
I'm sure the worst is behind us.
Just a second.
Ah!
I got it.
Fire!
Huh?
Oh my.
Get out.
Oop. Stay down.
Oop.
Everything will be fine.
Omni was ready.
Shotgun, it's not your day.
You sure your mother let you go to
school like that? Duh, Bob.
Duh, Bob.
Hi.
Well, you guys have a nice day.
So,
what do you do all day?
Nothing. I'm four.
You're full of it. Yeah, full of it. I'm
telling you, I downloaded it yesterday.
Really? Cuz if you really had that, it'd
be pretty cool. Yeah, pretty cool. Let's
hear it, then.
Trying to pop our ears is nothing but a
bunch of static. I don't get it. I get
it. You're a pathetic little nerd and a
liar. Let's get him.
Yeah!
Frankie, put me down! Put me down!
Put me down! Okay, you asked for it.
You guys are going to hear from me and
my lawyer. I'm going to sue you freaks,
each and every one of you!
So,
tell me more about Halloween.
It's the best. You get candy.
Everyone pretends to be someone else,
and nobody knows who you really are.
Sounds so familiar.
Nora.
So, what do you want to be? A
Frankenstein?
A zombie?
Sweetie, do you want to be a princess?
Yeah.
Okay.
Princess.
Laura.
Not really. Princess. Princess.
Princess.
Tada!
Pink.
Tada! Princess.
It's too big.
Too big?
Okay.
Laura.
>> [screaming]
>> Oh, sorry. Sorry.
Sorry.
Oh.
Laura!
Please don't wander off again.
I'm sorry, Bob.
Let's go pay for your costume.
Yo, he's home.
Just hold him till I get there.
Can I just say before we begin that only
in the current distressed condition of
the American public school system could
I be deposited headfirst into a garbage
can and yet I'm the one who winds up
receiving disciplinary action?
Who exactly are you? Oh.
I'm his mother's uh um
Neighbor. Neighbor. I'm
watching them for a few few days.
Well, this is not the first time Ian has
been in trouble. He gets in fights, he
lies.
>> Hey, I don't lie. You told everyone you
invited
Selena Gomez to the spring dance. Her
appearance fee was an obstacle. You said
you spent New Year's Eve at the Playboy
Mansion. Hey, pay-per-view high def. I
felt like I was there.
I'm telling you lying is a dangerous
game. Bob, you still have pins. What do
you
Oh, no. That's them. Who? The future
felons put me in the trash can.
Hey geek boy, we got detention because
of you. Yeah, because of you. You're
going to pay for that. Gentlemen, we
don't want trouble. Who's this? Your
mom? You wish. He's my bodyguard. I
hired him. You better watch out. That
true? No, he's joking.
I'm their babysitter. What are you going
to do?
Ask you politely to allow us to pass.
>> [laughter]
>> How humiliating. Why didn't you do
something?
Why did you tell them I was your
bodyguard?
You're right. I guess it was too big a
stretch.
Hey, how you doing? I'm Ian. If I told
you you had a beautiful body, would you
hold it against me?
Ew.
At least you're not shy.
I wanted to talk to her in the worst
way.
Mission accomplished.
>> [laughter]
>> You look so pretty.
Farren, I didn't know you did
gymnastics.
Why would you?
You don't know anything about me. You
come over to hang out with Jillian, and
you never even talk to us.
Come on, let's go.
The woman's got a point.
You don't know who you're sending out to
buy my clothes, but I want them killed.
You could go yourself. I'm the most
wanted man in America.
I cannot exactly browse the racks of
J.C. Penney's. Just give me something
that will blend in.
Something extremely American.
>> Sir,
we are ready to run the test.
Magnificence.
She must have plastic in her shoes. It
will eat any petroleum product.
We're working on that.
What happened to the bacteria? They live
as long as they feed. Once the oil is
gone, they disappear.
Just like my Jimmy Choos.
>> [applause]
>> Come in.
Let's talk about today. You could have
stood up for me, you know. I have to
face those guys. So, face them.
Unless you want to spend the rest of
your life with your head in the trash
can.
Thanks for the advice, Bob. All my
problems are solved.
They assign this in middle school? No,
that's my pleasure reading.
You smart.
You have a lot going for you.
Why do you make things up? Girls aren't
exactly impressed by astrophysics.
Given the resources, I could design,
build, and launch a rocket that would
accurately circumscribe an orbit of the
moon.
But,
other guys can, you know, throw a ball
through a hoop.
I don't want you to get in trouble.
I'll make you a deal.
If you try to tell the truth from now
on,
I won't tell your mother about your day.
Really?
Dude, that's almost cool.
You mean for a guy who sells pens?
Come on, kids. Time for bed.
Come on, one more spoonful.
Nora.
When the tree breaks, the baby falling
out
and really laying on the ground when the
bough
>> [crying]
>> This one.
I learned it in China when young.
Down came the
>> [singing]
[singing]
>> It's me.
I need your help.
I had to make up one heck of a yarn to
get all this stuff. What did you tell
them? Well, let's just say if I don't
find some weapons-grade uranium by dawn,
I'm in trouble.
What do you need all this for?
Get the kids ready for school.
Well, it's like my mom always used
[music] to say when she was stationed
over in East Berlin, she'd say, "Spying
is easy. Parenting's hard."
Good luck.
Bring it on.
Darren, you we need your help.
Mommy, in.
Darren.
Darren, you we need your help.
Mommy, in.
Darren.
>> Hey.
I guess it's my turn.
And Pharah, please put on a longer
skirt.
This means war.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Laura.
>> [music]
Stay with Bob.
>> Where is he hiding?
He's probably going to trick us into
opening the door.
Help me put these away.
Mhm.
>> Yeah.
You know the rules.
No soda upstairs.
What?
>> [music]
>> Breakfast is served.
All right, I'm going to bed.
Nighty night.
It's a school night. You should be
asleep.
How'd you find me?
Call it a hunch.
Why do you call your mother Jillian
instead of mom?
She's not my mom.
What do you mean?
My father was married before.
And my real mom died when I was little.
Jillian is just my stepmother.
And Ian and Nora are just my half
brother and sister.
I'm like the freak of the family.
It must have hurt your feelings when he
left. He'll be back for me.
I know he's not the greatest dad in the
world, but he loves me. And he's not
going to leave me here alone.
Anyway,
you should not climb the roof like this.
It's not safe.
Please don't tell me I can't come up
here.
It's like the only place I can chill.
Actually, I was going to offer to build
your railing.
Are you trying to bribe me into liking
you?
I just want you to be safe.
May I I chill with you?
It's a free country.
A little stuff.
Good news.
We got an address.
Good.
Take some men. Get that download back.
Tatiana.
No survivors.
Hey boss, you like?
No like?
May I make a couple of fashion
suggestions?
Women don't like the shirt tuck in.
Mess up your hair.
You know about fashion? No, but I know
women.
Wear it like this.
It's cool.
I saw it in the movie.
What movie? Octopussy? This isn't 1985.
I almost forgot.
What's this? Iggy Pop and David Bowie in
Shanghai. What? This is only about the
hardest concert to find in the world. I
guarantee you no one else in the school
district has it. You downloaded this for
me? Don't worry, I pay for it. How did
you even know about it? Easy. I was
there.
Bob, you're getting too efficient. We're
half an hour early. You're welcome.
Have a great day.
Hey, cool look, Aaron. Thanks. It's Ian.
Whatever.
>> [music]
>> Have a great day.
Look, the talk on the roof the other
night doesn't mean we're friends.
God forbid.
Dada, be right here. There is nobody
around. I found the computer, but the
file was downloaded to an external
storage device. I can't find that.
Or should I say that
I think I just figured out who lives
here.
Agent Ho.
Hello.
You must stop shooting things, Natasha.
I said it would be bad if the CIA or
Chinese had it. But she's both.
Find him.
But keep him alive.
I need to know who else he sold it to.
Listen up now.
Everybody,
you hear?
We must locate Chinese intelligence
agent Bob Ho.
He's very tricky, the best of the best.
He won't be easy to fight. Um Miss
Krysta
>> you mention you are genius, highly
trained, and you want to disappear. I
see him climbing with a bunch of skulls
on a rope.
Okay, he's not Conan the Barbarian. Good
try, though. No, I see him. There.
Go. Go.
Get him up. Get him UP. GET UP. DON'T
KILL HIM YET. We need information.
GET HIM UP.
>> [screaming]
>> COME HERE, SWEETHEART. GET BACK HERE.
COME HERE.
HUH.
>> Let go.
LET GO.
CAN YOU HOLD MY TURTLE? NO, NO.
You will pay for that, little man. You
princess.
Again, again, again.
Okay.
Why did you pull us out of school?
Who cares? We're out. Why are you in the
front seat anyway? It's my day.
>> No, it isn't. It's my day.
>> No, it's not your day. You're a liar.
Today is my day. It's my day.
You're a liar.
No. No.
I'm still hungry.
Doesn't look like they have chicken
tendrils to you.
We need to sign out of the make a call.
This is Firefly.
This is Bob Hole. I need help.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, so I get pretty good grades at
this university. I'm top of the class. I
don't like to brag, but you know.
Bob, this is Larry. Please meet you,
sir.
Let's get some food.
He goes to university. He's a poet.
Isn't it cool?
His rag is awesome. This is chicky
fashishy. It's bomb.
Let's go.
Hey.
How embarrassing.
You know, most people don't like me when
they first meet me. But Larry did.
I have two words for you, Larry.
13.
Ask the gold.
All right, Nora.
Come on.
You two stay at the table.
No, no, no.
I can't go in there.
Those are pigs.
>> [snorts]
>> Careful.
The lion jumped on me, and I killed him
with my bare hands, and I saved the
colonel's life. You're brave. [laughter]
Thanks.
How about this, Bob? The whole
restaurant and the waitress sat Larry
here. Isn't it great? It's like it's
fate or something. Really, sir, we're
just goofing around. Hey, Nora. Knock
knock. Who's there? Irish stew.
Irish stew who?
I will stew in the name of the law.
>> [laughter]
>> Larry's telling me all about the
university. It sounds great. Glad to
give you a tour sometime. When pigs fly.
It's not up to you. You're not my dad.
No, but I know that your mother hasn't
completely lost her mind.
It's just adorable. It's not like he's
asking me out on a date or anything.
Are you?
No, it's just a friendly offer.
Even if it was a date, you still
couldn't stop me.
What's your major, Larry?
English lit.
Would you pass the soy sauce?
That way I
get a background in the classics.
It's impossible. Пожалуйста.
You speak Russian?
Larry.
What's going on?
>> [groaning and screaming]
>> This is going to be painful.
You're right about that.
Go, go, go.
Maybe you write a poem about this.
Goodbye, Larry.
Oh.
>> [screaming]
>> Oh.
>> Fine, he's too old for me. Bob, I don't
want to be a princess anymore. I want to
be a cyborg.
How do you find us so fast? Doesn't make
sense. Bob, what's going on? Please be
quiet. I'm trying to think.
All right. All right. Fine. Fine.
I am international spy on loan to the
CIA from the Chinese intelligence
service. Someone wants me dead. And
Larry was a Russian operative, okay?
Fine. Don't tell us.
Cool.
Why won't you come along?
Stay here.
No.
Where are the kids? Inside.
Nothing else matters until these kids
are safe. Nothing. Of course. Colton set
up that safe house for him like you
requested. Okay.
Got that file on you?
What file? The one Colton linked you to
from Poldark's computer, your download.
I didn't download it.
I never even got it open.
Don't be asking me, Bob. It's classified
material. I need all copies. Why would
you think I downloaded it?
Unless someone told you I had. Someone
who wanted it back. Let's not make this
thing harder than it has to be, Bob.
Give me the file.
You're career officer.
Why do this?
>> out, same as you. We're both leaving for
love. Only I love money, and Anton
Poldark is match.com. The file.
Hey.
IT IS.
>> [screaming]
>> GOOD WORK.
NO.
CAN I JUST SAY YOU ARE by far the
coolest guy my mom has ever dated?
At least now I know how they keep
learning files so fast. How? The watch.
Chris told me to keep the watch. It must
have a tracking device.
Wow.
You really are a spy.
Gillian is totally going to freak.
What are you doing?
There's iron in these rocks. It will
hide the signal. Watch, please.
You realize if I told anyone at school
this story, I get detention for a year
for lying.
Yes? Hey partner, where you at?
Why do you ask? I needed to pick up that
file I sent you.
You know the one I want you to open for
me?
Bob? You there?
Bob.
I never saw you with so little product.
Hey, that's crazy, man. Something's
wrong. We need to get together and talk.
Nice try.
Bob?
Bob.
We'll be safe here. I promise. This is
your plan? Hide out in a hotel? Doesn't
look like they have chicken tenders
here, either.
>> This is awesome. Can we order room
service? Are you crazy? I'm going home.
No.
The only place you are safe is with me.
Safe with you? Everybody's trying to
kill you. I know. Isn't it cool?
Hey Bob, if you want to marry my mom,
I'll personally write the invitations.
Aw.
Love you, Bob.
Be realistic, Bob.
Hello. Hi Jillian. Hi sweetheart.
Yeah, grandpa just fell asleep. I was
going to call you guys.
I have to tell you something.
I know this is going to hurt you, but I
have to tell you.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
It's about Bob. What about him?
He's not who you think he is. He's a
spy, a Chinese spy, and these terrorists
are trying to kill him, and now the CIA
is after him, too, and they Baron, I
know you don't like Bob, but come on.
I'd expect this from Ian, but not from
you. What?
No, it's true. He's going to get us all
killed. Don't you even care?
Faran, this conversation is over. Put
Bob on.
Hi, Jillian. Bob, I am so sorry. I don't
know what's gotten into her.
It's true.
What is?
Everything she said is all true.
Whatever this is, it isn't funny.
Our kids are safe. I promise I'll give
them to you as soon as you get back.
You're either telling me the truth or
I've left my kids with a nut job.
Either way, you should come and get
them.
So, you got any other cool spy stuff
besides the watch?
Don't touch.
It's a very sharp.
Cool. What else?
>> [music]
>> Cool.
Yeah. Uh
Sorry, mister.
Airport, step on it.
>> [snorts]
[snorts]
>> Um
are you awake?
Are you kidding?
Does he always snore like that?
Can't you hear him next door?
I always thought it was the pig.
It's over with you and Julian, isn't it?
Yes, Faron, it's over.
You win.
Then why don't I feel like I won?
If you really loved her, you wouldn't
give up this easily.
It's because I love her
and the three of you
that I have to walk away.
It's more important [music]
that you are safe.
I thought I could put my other life
behind me, but I can't.
Be glad.
You're lucky you're not joining this
family.
You've no idea what it's like to live in
a place where you totally don't belong.
Don't be so sure.
I was an orphan.
I was raised in a group home.
I never knew my parents,
but I had a family.
I had a dozens of uh brothers and
sisters there,
and I wasn't related to any of them.
But I loved them all.
Family isn't whose blood you carry.
It's who you love
and who loves you.
>> [snorts]
>> Julian!
Come on.
>> Gillian,
I'm really sorry about everything.
Tell me the truth.
Are you really a spy?
Yes, I am.
I was going to tell you at dinner, but
you stopped me.
I don't care.
You put my children in danger.
Just go.
Bob,
when are we going to see you again?
You're not.
Please, don't go.
Who's going to sing me Chinese songs?
You'll be safe. I promise.
Stay away from my children.
>> [music]
>> Dear Mom, I am very sorry, but I cannot
stay here. My destiny is to be a spy
like Bob.
I am going with him.
Best wishes, your son, Ian.
Phone signal just popped back up.
We got him.
That's wrong.
Bob!
Ian!
You left your watch. What are you doing
here?
Let's go.
What do you mean?
We just got here.
>> Bob Hope.
What a coincidence.
Tie them up.
What are you doing here here?
I'm coming with you. I want to be a spy,
too.
Is this spy guy?
I thought he'd be better dressed.
How did you find me? I found one of your
tracking devices and put it in your
pocket when I hugged you goodbye. I'm
impressed. Thanks. Can we go back to
business? What the hell do you mention
I'm retired? Retired men don't download
secrets. I never download anything. He's
lying.
Who are you going to believe? Me or the
traitor?
Someone has been a very naughty boy.
He's got cameras and microphones mounted
all over the place. Huh, good plan film
meals together.
How could you turn against your country?
Simple.
I'm going to be a billionaire.
That file that you didn't download, it's
a formula for a growth bacteria hybrid.
The stuff literally eats oil.
Can you imagine?
Overnight, all the world's oil supplies
go poof.
All except for Russia's.
It'll be priceless, right, comrade?
How did you get Colt to go along with
you? Colt? That hillbilly is not part of
this. He doesn't know what goes on in
the real world. He still thinks
wrestling is real.
Let the boy go. He has nothing to do
with this. Mr. Tchetchet, just laid out
our whole plan.
We cannot let him go.
He will tell. Trust me.
No one will believe him.
He's right about that.
Hey boss, look at what I found sneaky
crooks.
Aaron?
Hi everybody.
Please,
have a seat.
This can't be happening.
Hold on. Let the children go. And I will
find this GBH file for you.
GBH? Like Stockholm GBH?
How do you know that? No freaking way.
You're telling me all this is because he
downloaded a bootleg concert? He did
what?
You downloaded it? Wow, these companies
take piracy way too seriously. You were
messing with my computer. It's private.
I just wanted to seem cool. You don't
need to. You are cool.
You are one of the coolest kid I know.
Really?
Thanks.
>> Hey, over here. Man with a gun. Wait a
minute. I am one of the only kids you
know.
Where is the file?
It's on my iPod on my desk at home.
Now see,
want to be a spy,
never tell the truth to the bad guy.
Sorry. I'm new at this.
Tatiana, take some men to the kids'
house and find the iPod.
What if the family is home?
Ever since you dyed your hair blonde,
kill them. No, don't.
Go. Bring me that iPod.
Come on, go. Go.
Now,
as for you,
stand still.
Freeze.
>> Awesome.
>> [screaming]
>> Fahrenheit, let's go.
I call shotgun,
then I pick the radio station.
Are you ready?
Hello. Jillian, listen to me.
Goodbye, Bob.
Jillian, wait. Don't hang up.
Jillian
Hang on. We've got to get there before
they do.
Is there anyone at the agency you can
still trust? [music]
Someone you can call? Sure, but they
took all my cameras. I have no proof of
anything.
Except that, as it happens, I recorded
that entire conversation on my cell
phone.
Way to go, dork.
Cody
Just listen. I'm going to play you
something.
The file that you didn't download, it's
a formula for a growth bacteria hybrid.
This stuff literally eats oil.
What is this? It's Halloween.
Don't yell at me.
What are you all doing out here? I
thought you were upstairs.
Everybody inside. Dad, we need to talk.
Mom, this isn't a joke. Do whatever he
says.
Give me your iPad. Is that an iPad? I
demand an explanation. They're coming.
Who? The Russians. Russians?
I saw them outside. They're coming.
Russians? Yes, Jillian. Russians. Let's
try and keep up.
It's too late. Everybody upstairs.
Understand [music] me?
Stay there.
Where's my stuff?
Here, take some of this stuff.
>> What is all this? Protection.
Why do you have a lighter? I don't want
you playing WITH FIRE.
>> [screaming]
[groaning]
>> OKAY, MAYBE JUST THIS ONCE. LET'S GO.
Trick or treat.
>> [laughter]
>> Hurry, close it. Close the curtain.
Okay.
I FORGOT JEFFY.
NORI.
What are you supposed to be? A cyborg
sent from the future. To blast you away.
Mommy, that man can fly.
I can't believe you did this to my
family. Endangering my kids. I didn't
mean to. I love your kids. I want to
marry you.
All four of you.
And I wanted to marry you. But our
wedding gifts would have to be opened by
the bomb squad.
>> All right, Thor. Enough games.
I finally found a normal guy, I thought.
Someone who likes to play.
Can we talk about this [music] later?
He switched bells.
Get him.
Give me the iPod, kid.
>> [screaming]
>> Come on. Let's TP the little geek's
house. Yeah, TP.
>> [groaning and screaming]
>> Hey, guys.
Got to go.
Maybe we should just stick to stealing
candy for little kids.
>> Yeah, real little kids.
This is going to be fun. Hey, Larry.
Knock knock.
>> [groaning and screaming]
>> Come on, guys. Get in the room. Lock the
door. Hurry. Lock it.
>> [screaming]
>> No.
>> I arrest you in the name of the law.
Sorry your retirement was so short, Bob.
You can kill me. Let the family go. I
can't. They seen too much. But I'll let
you go first so you don't have to watch.
Hey mister.
Don't think this changes anything.
EVERYBODY FREEZE.
It's okay.
Yeah, took you guys.
You stink, you low life.
Come on.
Let's go.
Come on, right there.
Who's in these things up? Oh, I'm sorry.
What's wrong? Got the handcuffs too
tight? I don't know how these things
work. I'm just a dumb hillbilly.
Everybody okay? Bumps and bruises. Yeah.
This really is the good guy.
Hey.
What you got there, son?
Nice work recording that conversation,
partner.
This young man might make a heck of a
spy someday. Uh-uh.
How quickly can you get me orange
jumpsuit?
I'm sorry I suspected you. Don't worry
about it, old buddy.
Chalk it up to the language barrier.
Thank you.
>> I'm sorry I put you through all this.
Goodbye, Jillian.
Goodbye, Krystal.
Bob!
I'm going to miss you.
I'm going to miss you, too.
Wait.
I know we lied.
But he did it to protect us. This whole
time all he ever wanted to do was
protect his mom.
Mom.
You're never going to find a man as good
as Bob. Never again.
Never.
I never thought I'd say this, but
I agree with Darren.
I suppose you have something to say,
too.
I want Bob to be my daddy.
>> [music]
>> Do you, Jillian, take Bob to be your
lawfully wedded husband?
I do.
And do you, Bob, take Jillian to be your
lawfully wedded wife?
Jillian,
there's one more thing I have to tell
you.
My name
really isn't Bob.
It's okay.
I do.
I now pronounce you man and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
>> [music]
[screaming]
>> No, that man's so crooked he could eat
nails and
Maybe he just want to fill up his gas
tank for free. I can't blame him. No,
that man's so crooked he could eat nails
and poop.
>> [laughter]
>> Sorry, mister.
>> Oh.
>> [applause]
[laughter]
>> What's going on?
Pop, I don't want to be a princess
anymore. I want to be a spy.
I'm an international spy on loan to the
CIA from the Chinese [music]
int-
from the Chinese intelligent intelligent
intelligence.
Well, I'll just pack a few things and
we'll be out of the house.
I am international spy on loan to the
CIA from the Chinese intelligent,
intelligent
I brought down dictators.
How tough is Xi Jinping?
Yes.
Maybe you write a poem about the
a poem about a poem.
Maybe you write a poem about
Maybe I write a
I hate English.
If a man marries you, he marries all
four of you.
Don't forget the pig, the cat, and the
turkey. And the turkey.
>> [laughter]
>> Turkey,
where did the turkey come from?
>> know. Yeah, from my grandmother's Sorry.
>> [music]
>> Ugh.
Grandmother's great. He plays
Cut.
When when they forget a dialogue, that's
me happy.
Good work.
Come out.
Camera needs you.
>> [laughter]
>> What are you doing?
What are you doing? We're filming. We're
making a movie.
Funny man.
Hey, camera mark.
Oh.
I'm going to lose
Mhm.
>> [music]
>> Woo.
>> Hey.